Ivaylo Tsochev

Sofia, Sofia City, Bulgaria

ivo.tsochev@gmail.com

+359895600503

linkedin.com/in/ivaylotsochev

Summary

Passioned about creating awesome websites and delivering the best user experience.

I started with online courses on Wordpress and later on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and lately with React, and creating my first websites for friends like portfolio websites and eCommerce.

Now working as a Web Developer is a dream come true and in my spare time working as freelancer projects for local business.

Wants to improve my self as a front-end developer and boost my React skills.

Feel free to contact me at ivo.tsochev@gmail.com and check my GitHub projects on this URL -> https://github.com/IvoTsochev

Experience



Frontend Developer

Vitamin Commerce

Feb 2020 - Present (2 years 5 months +)

Technical Support Specialist

GoDaddy

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Sales Representative

Telenor

Mar 2012 - Jan 2018 (5 years 11 months)

Education



Software University (SoftUni)

Software Engineer

2019 - Present

Великотърновски университет "Св. св. Кирил и Методий"

bookkeeping and control, Accounting 2007 - 2011

Licenses & Certifications

© Complete Python Bootcamp: Go from zero to hero in Python 3 - Udemy UC-OAHRELHL

- Programming Basics with Python Software University (SoftUni)
- Web Developer: Zero to Mastery Udemy UC-2WGBCZSV
- JS Fundamentals Software University (SoftUni)
- HTML & CSS Software University (SoftUni)
 df64d149
- CSS Advanced Software University (SoftUni)
 98ad1f55
- ReactJS Software University (SoftUni)
 120bfe2d
- Agile Fundamentals with Scrum Software University (SoftUni) a9f25515

Skills

JavaScript • SASS • Front-end Development • Web Design • Web Development • Responsive Web Design • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • WordPress • React.js

Honors & Awards

Customer First Hero - Telenor Group May 2016

Encouragement award from Telenor